barrysbootcamp.com 2018-09-08

# Privacy Policy - Barry’s Bootcamp

## **Barry’s Bootcamp Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us.  The page below goes over in detail how we approach your data – the summary is….our intentions are honorable.

This policy explains how we use your data and how we protect your privacy when you use our website and contact us by phone and email, as well as explaining our use of CCTV. As our services develop we will continue to update and review this policy to comply with both the law and customer feedback.

Barry’s Bootcamp understands the importance of your privacy, and we want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our site and using our services. This privacy policy governs the manner in which Barry’s Bootcamp collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [www.barrysbootcamp.com](http://www.barrysbootcamp.com/) website. This privacy policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by Barry’s Bootcamp. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information.  You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## What is personal data?

Personal data is data related to a living individual who can be identified from that data. This can also include special categories of personal data (personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, and genetic data, biometric data, health data and data concerning a person’s sex life or sexual orientation) and personal data relating to criminal convictions and offenses.

## **Who is responsible for the processing of your personal data?**

The Barry’s Bootcamp entity responsible for the processing of your personal data will depend on how you interact with Barry’s Bootcamp (whether via our website or other communications channels, or at our physical sites) and where you are located in the world. The relevant Barry’s Bootcamp entity is referred to as “Barry’s Bootcamp”, “our”, “we” or “us” in this privacy policy.

Please see the table below for the name of the Barry’s Bootcamp entity responsible and the appropriate contact information:

**United States of America  
**Barry’s Bootcamp LLC (7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

 **United Kingdom**  
Barry’s Bootcamp Limited (16 Upper Woburn Place, London, WC1H 0AF) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain UK-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC (7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

**Canada  
**Barry’s Bootcamp (310 Richmond St., West Unit 1, Toronto, Ontario M5V0B4) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain Canada-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC(7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.  

**Norway  
**Barry’s Bootcamp (Nonnesetergaten 4, Bergen 5015) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain Norway-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC(7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

 **Sweden  
**Barry’s Bootcamp (Kyrkogatan 58, 411 08, Gothenburg) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain Sweden-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC(7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

 **United Arab Emirates**  
Barry’s Bootcamp (Central Park Towers – Ground Floor, DIFC, Dubai) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain UAE-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC(7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

 **Italy**  
Barry’s Bootcamp (Via Senato 36 – 20121, Milano, Italy) is responsible for your purchases of products and services, and for your participation in certain Italy-based events and promotions.

For all other processing in the context of our website, Barry’s Bootcamp LLC(7373 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036) is responsible.

From time to time, it may be necessary for one Barry’s Bootcamp company to share your personal data with another Barry’s Bootcamp company.  For example, if you are a member of Barry’s Bootcamp UK and you wish to visit a Barry’s Bootcamp site in the USA, the UK company will provide to the US company the personal data necessary for you to book into a class in the US.  Your personal data may also be shared by all other Barry’s Bootcamp companies with Barry’s Bootcamp LLC, to enable Barry’s Bootcamp LLC to assist with any issues when using our website and to enable us complete the processing activities described in the “How and why we use your information” section below.

## Our Website

We may collect personal identification information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Mailing address
  * Telephone number
  * Credit card information 

Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, but this may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.

We may also collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our website, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilised and other similar information.

Where we do collect your personal data, this information is required for us to validate who you are, to deal with your queries effectively and to ensure that we can monitor usage of our sites as you sign up for classes. 

If you book in to attend one of our classes, we will also collect information relating to your health status and any physical impairments that might impact upon how you can use our services.  This is to ensure that we take your health record into account and can enable you to consider whether it is safe for you to attend our classes.

## Contacting us by telephone and email

_Contacting us by telephone_

We do not record telephone conversations or calls that you make to us.  During calls, we may however collect the following information:

  * Name 
  * Contact details
  * Your Barry’s Bootcamp account email address

We process this information because it is necessary for the performance of our contract with you, and to enable us to deliver services to you which you have requested and/or resolve any queries that you might raise when you call. 

_Contacting us by email_

Our email correspondence may be kept as a record of your contact with us, and to enable us to respond to any queries that you may have.

## CCTV

CCTV is installed at some of our sites, to monitor building security and assist in crime prevention and

detection.

We operate our CCTV in accordance with the guidance issued by the local data protection authority

in each country. Barry’s Bootcamp collects this data as part of its role as a service provider to you, and to ensure the health and safety of our staff and visitors to our sites.

We will not hold images for longer than necessary and will dispose of them securely.

##   **How and why we use your information**

We collect and process personal information about visitors to our website, clients, customers and users of/visitors to our sites.  We do this in order to deliver services to you, deliver merchandise to you when you make a purchase, process payments that you make to Barry’s Bootcamp and learn how to offer you a better product.

We may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes, all of which is for our legitimate interest of delivering services and products to you, and/or where it is necessary for the performance of our contract with you:

  * **To improve customer service** – Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support your needs more efficiently.
  * **To personalise the user experience** – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our website.
  * **To improve our website** – We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **To process payments** – We may use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * **To run a promotion, contest, survey or other feature** – To send users information which is relevant to services that they have purchased from us.
  * **To send periodic emails** – We may use the email address to send users information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their enquiries, questions, and/or other requests. We may also send emails to users that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Cookies

Our website may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly or optimally.

To find out more about cookies, you can visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

## Who we share with?

Like virtually every company, we do use third party companies to provide some parts of our service, so when you are making payments for example, you will need to give your payment details to our payments provider.  Rest assured the people we work with are trusted by millions and have excellent safeguards themselves.

We may also have to disclose your personal details if required by law.

If we do share your information with other organisations, we will have sharing protocols in place to ensure the organisation’s compliance with local data protection laws. 

We will not use your personal information for third party marketing purposes without your prior express consent.

We do not sell, trade, or rent users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information (i.e. in an anonymised form) regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Please note that the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you navigate to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

## How we store information?

We take our data protection responsibility very seriously and adopt and maintain high standards in respect of handling personal information. Your personal information will only be collected if it is necessary and proportionate to do so. 

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website.

Sensitive and private data exchanged between our website and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

With regard to disposal of your information, we will not hold your information for longer than we need to and when we dispose of it we will destroy paper and electronic copies in a secure way.

## Your rights

If you wish to see a copy of the personal data we hold about you then you can ask us at any time and we will respond within the time periods laid down in local data protection laws. 

Under certain circumstances, you also have the right to:

  * Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. 
  * Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it.
  * Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. 
  * Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
  * Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.

Where we process your personal information because we have your consent to do so you may withdraw your consent at any time.  

You can make a request in relation to any of the rights set out here by contacting the relevant Barry’s Bootcamp company and using the contact details for the relevant country set out in the “Who is responsible for the processing of your personal data?” section above.  Alternatively, you can contact us using the details set out in the “Contacting us” section below. 

If you wish to make a complaint about how we are processing your personal information you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the local data protection authority. You can find out how to contact the ICO on their website, [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)). 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Barry’s Bootcamp has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Barry’s Bootcamp or its services, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Barry’s Bootcamp  
[323-452-0037  
](tel:\(323\)%20452-0037)[323-452-0120](tel:\(323\)%20452-0120)  
info@barrysbootcamp.com

This Privacy Policy has been updated and effective as of June 1st, 2018.
